free-financial-advice.net 2014-04-03

# Free Financial Advice - Disclaimer and Privacy Policy

## Please Read Our Disclaimer and Privacy Policy if You Have Any Concerns

**Disclaimer**

The information contained on this website and from any communication related to this website is for information purposes only. 

Free Financial Advice does not hold itself out as providing any legal, financial or other advice. Free Financial Advice also does not make any recommendation or endorsement as to any investment, advisor or other service or product or to any material submitted by third parties or linked to this website. In addition, Free Financial Advice does not offer any advice regarding the nature, potential value or suitability of any particular investment, security or investment strategy. 

The investment and services mentioned on this website may not be suitable for you. If you have any doubts you should contact an independent financial advisor. In particular some of the investments mentioned may not be regulated under the Financial Services Act 1986 or at all and the protection provided to you under this Act will not apply. 

The material on this website does not constitute advice and you should not rely on any material in this website to make (or refrain from making) any decision or take (or refrain from making) any action.

This website contains links to other websites which are not under the control of and are not maintained by Free Financial Advice. Free Financial Advice is not responsible for the content of those sites. Free Financial Advice provides these links for your convenience only but does not necessarily endorse the material on these sites. 

Free Financial Advice does not make recommendations for buying or selling any securities or options. We make financial suggestions and it is up to our visitors to make their own decisions, or to consult with a registered investment advisor when evaluating the information on Free Financial Advice.

If you respond to Free Financial Advice via email or other correspondence, your comments or questions may be reproduced on this site.  If you don't approve of this, please don't send an email with questions or comments to us, or state specifically in your email that you do not want your information replicated on the site.

We respect your privacy and will never knowingly reproduce any personal information that would jeopardize your privacy.

**Advertising Privacy Policy:**

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).
